<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="simple.xsl" ?>
<product_details>
<product>
<name>1. Accuchek</name>
<PRICE>50</PRICE>
<description>is a drug administered orally or intravenously and is used for treating chronic gout arthritis.</description>
<sold>650</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>2. Charak</name>
<PRICE>100</PRICE>
<description>Charak is an antibiotic used for treating certain bacterial infections. It belongs to the class of antibiotics known as fluoroquinolones.</description>
<sold>900</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>3. Depura</name>
<PRICE>40</PRICE>
<description>Depura a antibiotic belonging to the penicillin group of drugs, which fights bacteria in your body. Amoxicillin is used to reduce the development of drug-resistant bacteria</description>
<sold>900</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>4. CTP</name>
<PRICE>159</PRICE>
<description>CTP is a mucolytic agent. It is used to treat respiratory disorders linked with viscid or excessive mucus.</description>
<sold>600</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>5. Digine</name>
<PRICE>200</PRICE>
<description> Digine is a third generation oral cephalosporin, effective against a wide range of sensitive gram-positive, gram-negative </description>
<sold>950</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>6. Everherb</name>
<PRICE>100</PRICE>
<description>Everherb is a broad-spectrum antibiotic, a bactericidal antibiotic, effective in Gram-positive and Gram-negative bacterial infections.</description>
<sold>2000</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>7. Kapiva</name>
<PRICE>40</PRICE>
<description>Kapiva is a bactericidal which is active against a wide range of Gram-positive and Gram-negative organisms. </description>
<sold>2000</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>8. Liveasy</name>
<PRICE>50</PRICE>
<description> Liveasy is an antibiotic belonging a class of drugs called cephalosporins. It is a second-generation cephalosporin antibiotic, which came to the markets of USA in 1977. </description>
<sold>250</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>9. ecosprin-75mg</name>
<price>25</price>
<description>ecosprin-75mg is an antibiotic belonging to the group of drugs called macrolide antibiotics. It is used to treat certain infections caused by bacteria </description>
<sold>500</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>10. Revital</name>
<PRICE>45</PRICE>
<description>Revital is a drug used for preventing and treating malaria. The disease is transmitted by the bite of a mosquito. The Chloroquine drug is also used for treating liver disease caused by protozoa.</description>
<sold>700</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>11. Seacod</name>
<PRICE>35</PRICE>
<description>Seacod is a semi-synthetic macrolide antibiotic, used for treating respiratory and urinary tract, soft tissue infections. </description>
<sold>750</sold>
</product>
<product>
<name>12. Hansaplast</name>
<PRICE>50</PRICE>
<description> Hansaplast is a highly lipophilic, long acting ACE inhibitor.The drug is used for treating blood pressure and congestive heart failure.</description>
<sold>300</sold>
</product>
</product_details>